apu.edu 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy - About This Site - Azusa Pacific University

Azusa Pacific University respects your privacy rights and has adopted clear guidelines for all of its departments and offices requiring that information you submit is only to be used for the purposes for which you have consented. Azusa Pacific University will never sell or rent any personal information collected from you to any third party. The following summarizes key points in our full privacy policy.

## General Data Protection Regulation

Current students, student applicants, employees, potential employees, or other individuals located in a European Union country, Iceland, Liechtenstein, Norway, or Switzerland who provide APU with personal data are now afforded new widespread privacy rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) effective May 25, 2018. Read the full GDPR Policy.

## Data Collection

  * We **do** collect personal information.
  * We **do** use cookies.
  * We **do** track online activity.
  * We **do not** allow third-party tracking.

Learn more about our data collection policies.

## Data Use and Sharing

  * We **do not** use your personal information without your consent.
  * We **do not** sell or rent your personal information.
  * We **do** use reasonable means to keep information secure.

Learn more about our data use and sharing policies.

## Privacy Rights

  * **You can** opt out or control how the information you submit online is used/shared
  * **You can** alter/update your information
  * **We have** a dispute resolution process.

Learn more about our privacy rights policies.

## Scope

This Privacy Policy covers information provided to Azusa Pacific University online at the following websites: 

  * Main APU Website
  * Graduate Online Application
  * Alumni Website

This Privacy Policy does _not_ cover information collected through means other than the APU websites listed above, and does _not_ cover the following internal Azusa Pacific University websites:

For more information, read the Office of Career Services’ [Privacy Policy (PDF)](https://www.apu.edu/live_data/files/157/privacy_policy.pdf).
